wallstreetotc.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy • Latest News in the Business and Financial World

  1. **INTRODUCTION**

Welcome to the Privacy Policy page of our website. This document, in addition to the [Terms of Use](https://www.wallstreetotc.com/terms-of-service/) of our website governs your use of the website. We understand and respect the need to know how your information is collected, stored and used. As such, this document provides information on all these fields.

By using our website and the services we provide, you agree to the terms set out in our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. If, at any time you are not satisfied with the provisions in either of these documents, you are advised to cease access and use of our website and services.

Please be reminded that we do not knowingly ask for or collect information on underage users. By accessing and using the website, you validate that you are at least 13 years old.

All content posted on our website is public. Therefore, do not share personal identification information either related to you or a third party, nor any proprietary information. We are not liable for any and all losses arising from doing otherwise.

  2. **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Personal Information** : In order to subscribe to our website and become a member of the online community, you will be prompted to share personal information such as but not restricted to full name, address, e-mail address, gender, age.

Personal information may be collected by us or from third parties. These include, but are not restricted to social media services, business partners or commercially available sources. For instance, if you share content from our website or access content on our website via a social media service, we may receive personal information such as, but not restricted to: your name, contact information, use of some applications, and information the said service has the right to share with us, such as profile image, friend list, email address.

Upon accessing our website or connecting our website to a social media service, you authorize us to collect and store personal information as the one described above in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Non-personal identifying information** : When accessing our website and services we may automatically collect information that is not personally linked to an individual. We make use of cookies and other tracking technologies (beacons, pixels, and browser cookies) to better understand how you use our website and services and be able to tailor the experience according to your needs.

This type of information includes but is not limited to geo-location, IP address, service provider, device used, operating system used, the number of pages you visit, the amount of time spent on pages, your interaction with the content.

Cookies and other tracking technologies collect information that is not personally identifiable. This type of information ensures a fluid and synergistic usage of the website, content and services.

Should you wish to disable cookies, most browsers enable you to do so. You can alternatively opt for a message to be prompted with every cookies set or updated. The Help section of your browser may help you in finding out more.

Blocking cookies or Flash technologies may lead to restricted access to certain features on the website, or personalized services.

**Log Files:** We may collect information such as, but not restricted to your browser, the platform you are using, the pages you access while using our website, the device you connect from, the name of the service provider, your IP address, your OS. All these are log files and they are not linked to personal information. Most times, this information is used for aggregate statistics that may be shared with third parties.

  3. **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use your personal information in relation to a request coming directly from you. Such cases include creating a user account or subscribing to our website and services. We thus use information about you and from you to offer you access to services and features on our website. We may also use your personal information to contact you.

Please be aware that all content posted on the website is public. Refrain from making any personal information available through any user-generated content. We are not responsible for any personal information disclosed as such.

In order to keep content and services on our website as close to your ideal experience as possible, we may combine Personal and Non-Personally Identifying Information we collect and store in relation to your use of our website and services.

  4. **HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

Personal information from you and about you is kept safe and not shared with third parties, except for cases that require us to do otherwise. These include but are not limited to protecting, enforcing and defending our legal rights, as well as our safety and property, and that of our affiliates, employees, contractors and agents; protecting against fraud, complying with applicable law in the case of disputes.

When generating content on our website, you are the sole responsible of the nature of the information you provide. Any and all information posted on our website is public and as such providing your name, location, email address, personal beliefs and other personal information is your responsibility.

Non-personal identifying information that we collect and store may be shared with third parties, such as but not restricted to our service providers, marketing partners or business partners. Aggregate information is used to tailor your experience with the services we provide and on our website.

All personal information from you and about you may be erased on your request. The information may be kept for longer under applicable law. Against this background, we will complete the deletion upon being relinquished from our lawful obligations. All information is erased from our active database. Information may be archived and used later under applicable law.

Institutions such as, but not limited to governmental agencies or law enforcement agencies may require us to disclose information we collect and store. We reserve the right to disclose information requested to the extent of applicable law.

  6. **INFORMATION SECURITY**

We respect your right to privacy and as such we strive to provide the most secure environment for the collection and storage of your information, both personal and non-personally identifying. We’ve put the system in place that should guarantee the security of information and protect against such instance as, but not limited to loss, unauthorized use, theft or modification.

However, no system is infallible. As such, if you have grounds to believe that your access and use of the website or any information you provided us is insecure or tackled with, please [contact us](https://www.wallstreetotc.com/contacts/) and notify the issue.

We do not guarantee the safety and security standards of your own software and hardware. We are not liable for any and all information loss or damages arising from security issues with your hardware and software.

  7. **CHILDREN PROTECTION**

Parents are advised to control their children’s online activity. Our website and the content provided here is not intended for children. In order to access our website and services, one must be at least 13 years of age. Unless you comply with this requirement, please cease accessing and using the website.

By accessing and using the website and services, you acknowledge you are above the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect and store any information on users below this age.

  8. **OTHER INFORMATION**

Our Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms of Use governing your use of the website and services may change periodically. Thus, we advise you to visit this page regularly and check the last date when the Privacy Policy was updated.

Continuing to access and use our website and services implies your agreement with both the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

If you have any questions, please do not hesitate to contact us.
